{
  "Statistics": [
    {
      "question": "Q1",
      "answer": "1",
      "solution": "dadffd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "bla",
        "badchoice1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q2",
      "answer": "blah",
      "solution": "dadffdddd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "bla2",
        "badchoice1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q3",
      "answer": "blah",
      "solution": "dadffdddd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "bla2",
        "badchoice1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q4",
      "answer": "blah",
      "solution": "dadffdddd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "bla2",
        "badchoice1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q5",
      "answer": "blah",
      "solution": "dadffdddd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "bla2",
        "badchoice1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q6",
      "answer": "blah",
      "solution": "dadffdddd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "bla2",
        "badchoice1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q7",
      "answer": "blah",
      "solution": "dadffdddd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "bla2",
        "badchoice1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q8",
      "answer": "blah",
      "solution": "dadffdddd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "bla2",
        "badchoice1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q9",
      "answer": "blah",
      "solution": "dadffdddd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "bla2",
        "badchoice1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q10",
      "answer": "blah",
      "solution": "dadffdddd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "bla2",
        "badchoice1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q11",
      "answer": "blah",
      "solution": "dadffdddd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "bla2",
        "badchoice1"
      ]
    }
  ],
  "APCal": [
    {
      "question": "cal1",
      "answer": 2,
      "solution": "NA",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "bla",
        "good"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "bla2",
      "answer": 0,
      "solution": "dadffdddd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "good",
        "bla2",
        "badchoice1"
      ]
    }
  ],
  "APCS": [
    {
      "question": "CS1",
      "answer": 2,
      "solution": "NA",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "badchoice2",
        "bla",
        "good"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "CS2",
      "answer": 0,
      "solution": "dadffdddd",
      "score": 1,
      "choices": [
        "good",
        "bla2",
        "badchoice1"
      ]
    }
  ]
}